It's all about payback.
Thick as Thieves is a drama, action, comedy film directed by Scott Sanders.
Two master thieves go at odds with one another as
one sets the other up for a crime.
The first, a suave pro who does his job and then hides in his own privacy,
listening to old jazz records and caring for his ailing dog, Wally.
The other is a local gangster with a taste for the finer
life, who decides to eliminate the competition.
This ignites a war between the two men and their aides.
An angry mob boss and a female police officer try to sort
the mess before things get too out of hand.
Mackin, played by Alec Baldwin.
Dink, played by Andre Braugher.
Pointy, played by Michael Jai White.
Petrone, played by Rebecca De Mornay.
Waiter, played by Mark Adair-Rios.
Janet, played by Khandi Alexander.
Thick as Thieves is a 1999 American crime film based on the novel of the same name by Patrick Quinn
and adapted for the screen by Scott Sanders and Arthur Krystal, with Sanders directing.
The film stars Alec Baldwin, Andre Braugher, Michael Jai
White, Bruce Greenwood and Rebecca De Mornay.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.